streetsine.com 2015-05-23

# Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement**

StreetSine respects your privacy and is committed to protecting personal information that we collect. The following is our Privacy Statement. When we gather and use information from you, we will comply with this policy as well as applicable Singapore privacy laws. We hope the following statement will help you understand how StreetSine collects, uses and safeguards personal information on our webSite. 

**Principles**

As a matter of principle, we try to minimize the amount of personal data we collect from you. We do not ask for more than that is required to service your account and provide the services you select.

As a Web 2.0 Site, StreetSine encourages you to share your wisdom with others by participating in such services as _Heard on StreetSine_ _TM_ , _StreetSine Quality Index_ _TM_ , business listings, and map amenities. However, this is done on an anonymous basis, unless you choose otherwise. 

StreetSine strives to provide open and transparent information about the Singapore property market. As a result, we make available past sales and rental prices for homes. We also allow users to comment on the market, businesses, and the community at large. Many times, this information is already publicly available. As long as the discussion is appropriate, involves real estate or other matters that concern the community, and does not single out individuals, we intend to keep this information freely available on the Site. 

StreetSine will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13. Our services are not designed to attract the attention of persons under the age of 13.

**Collection and Use of Information**

The information that we collect and employ from our users fall into the following five categories:

  1. Personal data. This is information that identifies you specifically. It may include name, mailing address, email address, national identity number and telephone or mobile number. We use this information to open an account, verify you are a unique visitor, and enable you to participate in _MyOrganizer_. _MyOrganizer_ allows you to contact sellers or agent and save and/or print information from the Site. With one exception we do not sell or give your personal data to third-parties. The one exception is that when you send a free SMS (or email) to the seller, your name and mobile number (or email) is sent to the seller in return for the seller’s contact information. This is a necessary step to validate the link between the buyer and the seller and establish a serious intent to transact. Of course, by taking the action to send a free SMS (or email), you consent to the sharing of this information with that particular seller. It is important to emphasize that the free SMS (or email) you send goes only to the seller of the property or business you selected.

  2. Business data. This information refers to data provided by a seller and displayed in property and business listings, or in a forum linked to them. The purpose of this data is to advertise the seller’s offering. It is data that an agent or seller uploads in the listings for display on the Site. It may include contact information, webSite links, text, housing information, etc. There are multiple places on the Site that this information might be displayed and they include: as part of a search list, on the map, in _MyOrganizer_ , in _Heard on StreetSin_ e, in an RSS feed, in a chart, etc. This data is not protected by this Privacy Statement because the business makes an active choice to make that information public. Also, please be aware that other Internet Sites, which share links to StreetSine, may contain privacy provisions that differ from this Privacy Statement.

  3. Seller data. This information refers to data that we collect to facilitate the seller’s management of his or her business data. It may include agent identification number and seller contact information. It may also include a report of the seller’s activity (i.e., status of listings, number of interested buyers, etc.) on the Site. Note that we do not collect credit card or related financial information. We employ PayPal, a secure, third-party payment system to handle payments for services rendered. It is also important to emphasize that we neither sell nor give individual seller data to third-parties. The specific contents of each management account are completely confidential. However, please note that StreetSine may track sales activity in the aggregrate but none of the results will be linked to the individual seller. The purpose of tracking activity in the aggregrate is to demonstrate to agents and sellers the usefulness of the Site as well as improve the Site’s performance.

  4. Web 2.0 data. This information refers to the wisdom and opinions that we collect from the Site’s users. This information is voluntaryly provided to the Site for public consumption and usually given anonymously. It may include the information that is collected and displayed in the ratings of amenities, _Heard on StreetSine_ _TM_ , _StreetSine Quality Index_ _TM_ , and the consumer portion of the business listings. This data is not protected by this Privacy Statement because the user makes an active choice to make that information public.

  5. User data. This is information that we collect in order to track how the user is using the Site. We may use "cookies," web beacons, and other technologies to collect this information. Examples of what we collect may include information on the server your computer is logged onto, your browser type (i.e., Firefox, Safari, etc.), your Internet protocol address, your selection of a StreetSine advertisements, and your selection of the various functions on the Site (i.e., search bar, listings, add to MyOrganizer, etc.) It is important to emphasize that this data is collected and tracked in the aggregate and not linked to you personally. We use this information to measure response rates to advertisements and usage rates of the Sites functions/services. These measurements, in turn, help us to improve the Site and our services to our users. Also, note that at any time, you may adjust settings on your browser to refuse cookies. However, if you choose to disable cookies, many of the free features and services on StreetSine will not operate properly. 

**Safeguards of Personal Information**

StreetSine processes and stores personal information from the Site in databases hosted in Singapore. We have taken reasonable steps to protect the information users share with us, including, but not limited to, setup of processes, equipment and software to avoid unauthorized access or disclosure of this information. We limit access to personal information only to StreetSine employees who are reasonably required to come in contact with that information in order to provide services to you or in order to do their jobs. ****

If you have any comments or questions regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact us via Feedback at the bottom of the Site. 

Please note that this policy may be amended. You should review the most current version before relying on any of the provisions in this Privacy Statement. 

_—_ _Updated April 2008_
